catchthemes.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy - Catch Themes

This is the Privacy Policy for . It describes how Catch Themes, LLC (known as “Catch Themes”, “We” or “Site”), the owner and operator of the  website, uses and protects any “Personal Data” that you give when you use this website.  
Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Data.

The CatchThemes.com Privacy Policy is designed to help you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decision when using our site and our products and services. Catch Themes is a web design agency specializing in WordPress themes and plugins.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

We collect information from you when you register, place an order, issue support ticket, subscribe to our newsletter, post your comment. In this process you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, website, mailing address, phone number, payment information or other details. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

When you browse our Site, we also automatically receive traffic data registered by the hosting servers, cookies that may share some personal data and your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address. We also use information offered by other external services of traffic analysis, such as Google Analytics.

#### What Do We Use Your Information For?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To administer and expand our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.
  * To process transaction
  * To send periodic emails
  * To provide you with updates, promotions and marketing information about products and services
  * To improve the quality of our website and products
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
  * For internal record keeping and statistical purposes
  * To notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

#### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. All supplied sensitive/credit information transmitted are encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

#### What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

#### Do We Use Cookies?

Yes we use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart
  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits
  * Keep track of advertisements
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to delete or turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings.  
If you disable cookies installation or you delete cookies from your computer’s hard disk you may be unable to use some of the features of our website, products and services.

#### Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### What About Other Websites Linked to This Site?

We may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old and our Site is not suitable for children under 13.  
For children from 13 years to full age, it is necessary the supervision of an adult or a guardian to register on Site and buy a product.  
It is the sole and unilateral responsibility of parents and guardians to monitor their children’s use of our Site.

#### Your Consent

By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with any changes.

The last update of this Privacy Policy was made on May 18, 2018.

#### Company info

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.  
Catch Themes, LLC  
2570 Bradford Sq, NE  
Atlanta 30345  
USA  
Email: info[at]catchthemes[dot]com
